{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Natural Stone Tile Installation Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40046/":{"taskOID":40046,"originalTaskOID":40046,"setID":370,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7017,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":8266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing Tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10422,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile for new construction","answerDisplayText":"Tile for new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200438,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the tile for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5331,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stone","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of stone would you like installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5481,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5844,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soapstone","answerDisplayText":"Soapstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6484,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Travertine","answerDisplayText":"Travertine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5490,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Tile Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where would you like to install stone tiles? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5332,"questionDisplayText":"Stone Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size stone would you like installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4 x 4 or smaller","answerDisplayText":"4 x 4 or smaller","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":535,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6 x 6","answerDisplayText":"6 x 6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":559,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8 x 8","answerDisplayText":"8 x 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":309,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10 x 10","answerDisplayText":"10 x 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":335,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"12 x 12 or larger","answerDisplayText":"12 x 12 or larger","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7017,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":8266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing Tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10422,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile for new construction","answerDisplayText":"Tile for new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing tile","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing Tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8265,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing non-tile surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10422,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile for new construction","answerDisplayText":"Tile for new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200438,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the tile for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5331,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stone","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of stone would you like installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5481,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5844,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soapstone","answerDisplayText":"Soapstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6484,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Travertine","answerDisplayText":"Travertine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5481,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5844,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soapstone","answerDisplayText":"Soapstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6484,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Travertine","answerDisplayText":"Travertine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5490,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Tile Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where would you like to install stone tiles? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5332,"questionDisplayText":"Stone Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size stone would you like installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4 x 4 or smaller","answerDisplayText":"4 x 4 or smaller","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":535,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6 x 6","answerDisplayText":"6 x 6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":559,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8 x 8","answerDisplayText":"8 x 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":309,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10 x 10","answerDisplayText":"10 x 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":335,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"12 x 12 or larger","answerDisplayText":"12 x 12 or larger","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4 x 4 or smaller","answerDisplayText":"4 x 4 or smaller","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":535,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6 x 6","answerDisplayText":"6 x 6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":559,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8 x 8","answerDisplayText":"8 x 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":309,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10 x 10","answerDisplayText":"10 x 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":335,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"12 x 12 or larger","answerDisplayText":"12 x 12 or larger","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40046/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40046,"taskName":"Tile: Natural Stone (Granite, Marble, Slate, Quartz, etc) - Install","taskDescription":"Install Natural Stone Tile","xmTaskDescriptor":"Natural Stone Tile Installation Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":392,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Stone Natural Slate Marble Granite","textMessagingName":"Install Stone Tile","rolloverLongDesc":"Installation or complete replacement tile on bars, countertops, vanities, mantels, hearths, walls \u0026 floors.","rolloverShortDesc":"Install new or replace marble, sandstone, slate, granite tile, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Natural Stone Tile.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Marble, Granite \u0026 Slate Tile Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Natural Stone Tile Install","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":74,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Natural Stone Tile Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tile: Natural Stone (Granite, Marble, Slate, Quartz, etc) - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Stone Tile Project","urlName":"Natural-Stone-Tile-Marble-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Marble, Granite \u0026 Slate Tile Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Natural Stone Tiles","searchKeywords":"Stone,Natural,Slate,Marble,Granite,Tile,Quartz,porcelain,flooring,floor,clean,ceramic,brick,tiles,mosaic, top,counter, countertops","emcCategoryOid":-12073,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":370,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}